pccwglobal.net 2013-04-03

# Privacy Policy Statement

**1.   Information collection**

In order to provide a better service to you, we may collect information when you register with us, use our services, attend our functions, or communicate with us. In the process, we also collect personal information about individual contact persons of the companies or their employees. If specific information is requested but not supplied, we may be unable to provide the requested service.

**2.    Use of information**

The purposes for which information may be used by us in and outside Hong Kong include:

  * providing services to facilitate services in or outside Hong Kong, and providing enquirers with contact and business information; 
  * distribution of PCCW Global’s publications and research materials (and those of our business partners and counterparties); 
  * marketing PCCW Global’s services or products (and those of our business partners and counterparties);
  * complying with the applicable laws in or outside Hong Kong; and
  * other related purposes. 

**3.    Disclosure **

We will keep the personal data we hold confidential but may provide information, for the purposes stated in paragraph 2 above, to:

  * our affiliates, overseas offices, business partners and counterparties
  * persons under a duty of confidentiality to us 
  * persons to whom we are required to make disclosure under any applicable laws in or outside Hong Kong 
  * personnel, agents, advisers, auditors, contractors, financial institutions, and service providers in connection with our operations or services 

**4.   Security**

Personal data stored electronically are password-protected. Encryption technology is used on our secured web areas. Our computer systems are placed in restricted areas which can only be accessed by authorized employees. These authorized employees are all well trained and made aware of their duties in respect of data security by reference to the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance and this Privacy Policy Statement. All practicable steps will be taken to ensure no unauthorized or accidental access, processing, erasure or other uses of the personal data held by us. ****

**5.    Hyperlinks [applicable to online user] **

Hyperlinks to other websites are provided for your convenience. You will leave our website for another location that is not controlled by us. Our privacy policies do not apply to other websites. Please refer to the privacy policies of the other websites.

**6.    Retention of personal data**

We will destroy any personal data it may hold in accordance with its internal policy.  Generally, personal data will only be retained for as long as is necessary to fulfill the original or directly related purpose for which it was collected, unless the personal data is also retained to satisfy any applicable statutory or contractual obligations.

**7.    Rights of data subjects **

Before collection of personal data from an individual, the individual will be able to access this Privacy Policy Statement and the Personal Information Collection Statement in which the information would help him/her determine whether to provide personal data.

Under the Hong Kong Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance, you being data subject have the right to:

  * ascertain  whether we hold personal data about you and to be provided with a copy of the data; 
  * require us to correct inaccurate data; andd
  * ascertain our policies and practices in relation to personal data.

Please send requests to access or correct data, questions or complaints to:

PCCW Global Marketing  
Email: [marketing@pccwglobal.com](mailto:marketing@pccwglobal.com)
